You don't understand.
你们男生不懂亲吻对女生的重要性
For us,kissing is as important as any part.
对我们而言，亲吻和其他任何部分一样重要
Yeah,right!
没错
You serious?
当真?
Oh,yeah.
当然
- Everything is in that first kiss. - Absolutely.
- 你想了解的一切全在初吻之中  - 没错
For us,kissing's an opening act..
对我们而言亲吻就像是开场
like the comedian you have to sit through..
就像佛洛伊飞船出场前
before Pink Floyd comes out.
你得耐着性子先看完脱口秀
And it's not that we don't like the comedian.
对，我们并非讨厌脱口秀
It's just that that's not why we bought the ticket.
只是那不是我们买票的原因
The problem is,no matter how great the show was..
问题出在于演唱会结束后 不论表演有多精采
you girls are looking for the comedian again.
你们女生总还想再看脱口秀
We're in the car,fighting traffic, just trying to stay awake.
我们在车上奋力杀出车阵  只是拼命让自己别睡着
Word of advice: Bring back the comedian.
是哦?给你一个建议 叫脱口秀主持人再度上场
Or next time you'll find yourself listening to that album alone.
否则下次，你们只能坐家里听唱片
Are we still talking about sex?
我们还在谈论性吗?
The One With the Sonogram at the End
六人行 第1季 第02集 参加助产训练班
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
No,it's good. It is good.
不，这样很好
It's just that Doesn't she seem a little angry?
只是她看起来是不是有点生气吗?
Well,she has issues.
她有麻烦事
Does she?
她有吗?
Try to live with "Mr. I'm Evolving."
他尝试和“参与者先生”生活在一起
He's out while she's home getting the mastodon smell out of the carpet.
他在外头乱搞女人  而她却待家里设法去除地毯上乳齿象的味道
Marsha,see,these are cave people.
玛莎，他们是穴居人
Okay,they have issues like:
他们关心的问题是
"Gee,that glacier's getting kind of close."
Gee，那条冰河愈来愈接近了
Speaking of issues, isn't that your ex-wife?
谈到麻烦事，那不是你前妻吗?
- No. - Yes,it is. Carol,hi!
- 不，那不是  - 是的，是卡箩，嗨
Okay. Yes,it is. I'll catch up with you in the Ice Age.
好吧，是她 我会到冰河期去找你
- Can I stay? - No.
- 我可以留在这吗？  - 要我说，不
- Hi. - Hi.
- 嗨. - 嗨
- Is this a bad time? - No,it's..
- 我来的时间不对？ - 不，这里是…
the Stone Age.
石器时代
You look great. I hate that.
你的气色好极了，我讨厌看到这样
Sorry. Thanks. You look good too.
抱歉，谢了！你的气色也很好
Well,you know, in here,anyone who..
好吧，在这儿任何人
stands erect..
直立行走的人…
- What's new? Still a - A lesbian?
- 最近如何? 还是… - 女同志?
You never know. How's the family?
问问无妨嘛，家庭生活如何?
- Marty's still totally paranoid. - Carol,why are you here?
- 玛蒂的疑心病还是很重  - 卡萝，为什么来这儿?
- I'm pregnant. - Pregnant.
- 我怀孕了  - 怀孕
She didn't leave in such a hurry after all.
她似乎不急着离开
This is the Three's Company episode with a misunderstanding.
这是“斯瑞家族公司”，他们有误会的那集
Then I've already seen this one.
我看过这一集
Are you through with that?
喝完没?
Sorry,the swallowing slowed me down.
抱歉，吞下去的时间太慢
Whose ball of paper is this?
这是谁的小纸团?
Mine. I wrote a note to myself, then I didn't need it.
我的，我写给自己一张便条 后来觉得自己不需要
So I balled it up and now I wish I was dead.
于是将它揉成纸团 现在我不想活了
She already fluffed that pillow. You already fluffed It's fine.
她已经拍松过那个枕头.  摩妮卡，你已经拍过了枕头了?
I just don't wanna give them any more ammunition.
我只是不想让他们有藉题发挥的机会
Parents can be cruel about the flatness of a child's pillow.
我们都知道父母对枕头平的孩子有多凶
Relax,you do this every time. The place looks great.
放松一下，你每次都这样  这里看起来已经很棒了
You got a lasagna here that looks good enough..
你这里有意大利烤面 这看起来好极了
to avoid touching.
还不许碰
Monica? Hi!
摩妮卡？嗨！
Monica,you're scaring me.
摩妮卡…你吓到我了
I mean,you're all chaotic and twirly,you know?
我是说，你现在这样子慌慌张张的
Not in a good way.
显得不是很好
Calm down. You don't see Ross getting twirly every time they come.
安心吧.你们没看过每次他们来时  罗斯慌张的模样
That's because my parents think Ross can do no wrong.
因为在我爸妈心目中罗斯不可能犯错
You see,he's "The Prince."
他是个王子
They had some big ceremony before I was born.
显然,他们在我出生前有个大型仪式
- What? - Ugly Naked Guy got a ThighMaster.
什么? - 丑陋裸男有个“美腿器”
- Has anybody seen my engagement ring? - It's beautiful.
- 有人看见我的订婚戒指吗?  - 有，很漂亮
Oh,God! Oh,God! Oh,God!
天啊! 天啊! 天啊! 糟了・，．
No,don't touch that.
嘿,不要动它们
Like I wasn't dreading tomorrow enough,having to give it back.
明天就要还他戒指 我似乎还不够担心
"Hi,Barry,remember me? I'm the girl that stomped on your heart."
“巴瑞，记得我吗?我是那个穿白纱  让你在亲友面前出糗的人”
Now I must return the ring without the ring..
天啊，如今我必须还他戒指 偏偏戒指不见了
which makes it so much harder.
叫我如何面对他
Easy,we'll find it. Won't we?
别急，我们会找到的，对不?
Look,it's gonna be okay. You'll give it back..
一切都会好的，我们会把它找回来的
- and we'll eat ice cream. - Okay. It's a pear-shaped diamond
- 而且我们会吃很多冰淇淋  - 好吧，是一个珍珠型的钻石
Any diamond ring we find, we'll run it by you.
不管我们找到什么样的钻石戒指都会给你的
- When did you have it last? - Doy,right before she lost it.
- 最後一次戴是在什么时候?  - “孩子”，大概是在遗失之前
You don't get a lot of "doy" these days.
这年头说“孩子”的人不多
I know I had it this morning.
我今天早上还戴它
I know I had it when I was in the kitchen with
我在厨房戴着做…
Dinah?
面条?
- Oh,don't be mad. - You didn't.
- 别生气 - 你不会
- Oh,I'm sorry. - I gave you one job!
- 对不起  - 我就让你做了这么一件事情
But look how straight those noodles are.
你看面条现在变得多直
That's not how you look for an engagement ring in a lasagna.
摩妮卡，在千层面中找订婚戒指不是那样找的
I just can't do it.
我办不到
Boys? We're going in.
我们很高兴做
Hi.
嗨. 各位
- That is not a happy "hi." - Carol's pregnant.
- 这可不是开心的“嗨”  - 卡萝怀孕了
I found it!
我找到了
What?
什,什,什么?
Yeah.
是的
Do that for two hours,you might be where I am about now.
你再持续两小时,就会变成我这样
That puts that whole pillow thing in perspective.
如此一来,枕头的事就可先揽在一旁?
How do you fit into this whole thing?
你现在要怎么办?
Carol and Susan want me to be involved.
卡萝说她和苏珊想让我加人
But if I'm not comfortable with it, I don't have to be involved.
但是对这件事我不太感到舒服, 我不想卷进去
- It's totally up to me. - She is so great. I miss her.
- 一切由我做决定  - 她人好好，我真想念她
- What does she mean by "involved"? - Your job is done.
- 她所谓的“加入”代表什么? - 你的阶段性任务已经结束了
And the most enjoyable.
也是最有意思的阶段哦
Phoebe,say something.
菲比，说点什么
They want me to go down to this sonogram thing..
她们要我去做超音波检查
with them tomorrow.
明天和她们两个一起
Remember when life was simpler..
记得当生活变得简单了…
and she was just a lesbian?
她也不过是个女同性恋了
Those were the days.
这就是生活啊
- What are you gonna do? - I have no idea.
- 你打算怎么做?  - 我也不知道
No matter what I do, I'm still gonna be a father.
不管我怎么做,我还是孩子的爹
This is still ruined,right?
面还是被搅乱了，不是吗?
Martha Lugwin's daughter is gonna call you.
玛莎路金的女儿会打电话给你
- What's that curry taste? - Curry.
- 怎么会有咖哩味?  - 因为有放咖哩?
I think they're great. I really do.
这东西很好吃，真的
The big Lugwin had a thing for you.
你还记得路金一家人吧?  老路金很惦记你
- They all had a thing for him. - Oh,Mom.
- 他们一家都很惦记你.  - 不要这样,妈妈
Why is this girl going to call me?
抱歉，她为何要打电话给我?
She just graduated,and she wants to be something in cooking or food..
她刚毕业,想找份烹饪的工作吧
I told her you have a restaurant
我告诉她你开了一家餐馆
- I don't have,I work in a restaurant. - They don't have to know that.
- 不，妈，我没开餐馆,不过是在餐馆工作  - 他们不需要知道
- Ross,help me with the spaghetti. - Yes.
- 罗斯，能帮我做意大利面吗?  - 好的
Oh,we're having spaghetti. That's easy.
我们吃意大利面呀?太简单了
We were going to have lasagna.
我们要吃意大利面了啊
- I love lasagna. - We're not having it.
- 我喜欢意大利面  - 不过我们没有意大利面
Then why bring it up? He latches on.
那为什么要提到这个呢？这下他就来劲了啊
This will sound unbelievably selfish..
我知道这样要求过于自私
but did you plan to bring up the baby/lesbian thing?
你能不能和他们说一下 小孩/女同性恋之类的事?
It might take the heat off of me.
因为这样可以让我喘口气
That Rachel. We saw her parents at the club.
那个瑞秋…我们在俱乐部碰到了她父母
They were not playing well.
他们很不开心
I won't say what they spent..
我不想讲他们为此婚礼花了些什么
but $40,000 is a lot for a wedding.
但是4万块不是个小数目?
At least she had the chance to leave a man at the altar.
至少她有机会把一个男人留在教堂里的圣坛
- What's that supposed to mean? - Nothing.
- 什么意思?  - 没什么
- It's an expression. - No,it's not.
- 随便说说而已  - 不，不是的
Don't listen to her. You've always been independent.
别听你妈乱讲话,你一直都很独立
Even when you were a chubby kid..
就连你小时候胖嘟嘟的
and you had no friends, you were just fine.
一个朋友也没有的时候，你还是活得好好的
You'd read alone in your room. Your puzzles..
你会待在你房里看书…玩拼图
People like Ross need to shoot for the stars.
而像罗斯这种人则追求卓越
With his museum and his published papers.
博物馆，出版论文…
Others are satisfied with staying where they are.
其他人则安於现状
These people never get cancer.
告诉你，这种人不会得癌症
They're happy with what they have,content..
他们对拥有的一切都很开心
like cows.
就像奶牛一样
Cows,Dad?
奶牛，爸爸？
She knows how much I love cows.
她知道我有多喜欢奶牛
I read about women trying to have it all,and I thank God..
我还知道这些女人想拥有一切，幸好
our "Harmonica" doesn't have that problem.
我们家的小摩妮卡…没有这种问题
- I'm telling you,you'll be fine. - Thank you,Daddy.
- 我跟你说，你很不错  - 谢谢，老爸
Oh,so this does work.
天哦，这个居然还能用
So,Ross,what's going on with you?
罗斯，最近你怎么样？
Any stories? No news,no little anecdotes to share with the folks?
最近有什么新闻八卦之类可以和老爸老妈分享的
Look,I realize you guys have been wondering..
好吧,我知道你们想了解
what exactly happened between Carol and me.
我和卡萝之间倒底怎么了
And so,well,here's the deal.
事情是这样的
Carol's a lesbian.
卡萝是个女同志
She lives with a woman named Susan.
她和一个名字苏珊的女人同居
She's pregnant with my child.
她怀了我的孩子
She and Susan are going to raise the baby.
并打算和苏珊共同扶养他
And you knew about this?
这些你全都知道?
Folks are really that bad?
你的状况真的很糟糕吗?
Well,you know,these people are pros.
你要知道这些人十分专业
They know what they do.
他们知道他们要做什么
They take their time. They get the job done.
他们会躲在那里,再来个突然袭击
They say that you can't change your parents.
常言道：父母是无法交换的
Boy,if you could,I'd want yours.
如果可以，我要你…的父母
Must pee.
我要去尿尿了
It's worse when you're twins.
如果你是双胞胎，情况会更惨
- You're a twin? - We don't speak.
-你是双胞胎?  -对，我们不往来
She's this high-powered, driven,career-type.
她是一心追求事业的人
- What does she do? - She's a waitress.
-她从事什么工作?  -服务生
- Identical? - People say we look alike.
- 你们俩长的一样吗？  - 大家都说我俩长的很像
But I don't see it.
但我不这么认为
You guys,I kind of gotta clean up now.
各位，我得打扫了
Chandler,as an only child, you don't have this.
钱德，你是独子?你没有这些困扰?
No,although I did have an imaginary friend..
没有，尽管我有个想像中的朋友
who my parents preferred.
而我爸妈比较喜欢他
Hit the lights,please.
帮我关灯
How long was I in there?
我在里面多久了?
- I'm just cleaning up. - Oh,you need any help?
- 我只是在打扫  - 需要帮忙吗?
Okay,sure. Thanks.
好呀，谢了
Anyway..
总之.
So you nervous about Barry tomorrow?
明天要见巴瑞，紧张吗?
A little.
有一点
A lot.
很紧张
So,got any advice?
有什么建议吗?
You know,as someone who's recently been dumped.
就一个最近刚被甩的人而言
You may wanna steer clear of the word "dumped."
你应该避免用“甩”这个字眼
Chances are he's gonna be this broken shell of a man.
更不巧的是现在他可能痛不欲生
You should try not to look too terrific. I know it'll be hard.
因此你不该显得艳光照人,我知道这一点很难做到
Or I'll go down there, and I'll give Barry back his ring.
这样吧，我拿戒指还巴瑞
And you can go with Carol and Susan to the ob-gyn.
你陪卡萝及苏珊去做检查
You've got Carol tomorrow.
你明天得见卡萝
- When did it get so complicated? - Got me.
- 此事何时变得这么复杂?  - 你可问倒我了
- Remember being in high school? - Yeah.
-还记得我们在高中时代吗?  -记得
Didn't you think you'd meet someone..
你没想过自己会遇见心上人
fall in love,and that'd be it?
恋爱,然後厮守终生吗?
- Ross? - Yes. Yes.
- 罗斯?  - 在.在
Man,I never thought I'd be here.
没想到自己会沦落到这个地步
Me neither.
我也是
Sorry I'm late. I got stuck at work.
抱歉，我迟到了,我忙得无法脱身于
There was this big dinosaur thing. Anyway..
那些大的恐龙之类的事情
Hi.
嗨
- You remember Susan. - How could I forget?
- 罗斯，记得苏珊吗?  - 我怎能忘得了?
Hello,Susan. Good shake,good shake.
你好，苏珊，她的手好有力啊…
So,we're just waiting for?
那么我们在等…
- Dr. Oberman. - And is he?
- 欧伯曼大夫  - 他…？
- She. - Of course,"she."
- 是“她” - 当然是…她
Is she familiar with our special situation?
她了解我们的特殊状况?
- Yes,and she's very supportive. - Okay,that's great.
- 了解，而且她非常支持 - 这太好了
No,I'm Oh.
不,我只是
Thanks.
谢了
That opens my cervix.
罗斯，那是用来打开我的子宫颈的
- Barry? - Come on in.
- 巴瑞  - 进来吧
- Are you sure? - It's fine.
- 进来吧  - 没问题?
Robbie's gonna be here for hours.
罗此得待在这儿好几个小时
So,how are you doing?
最近好吗?
I'm..
我…
I'm okay.
我很好
- You look great. - Yeah,well.
- 你的气色好极了  - 是的
Dr. Farber,Jason Greenspan's gagging.
法大夫，杰森快没气了
Be right there. Be back in a second.
马上到,我马上回来
I dumped him.
我甩了他
So,how's this all gonna work?
我们该如何处理此事?
The baby grows in a special place inside
婴儿在母亲身体中一个特殊的部位生长
Thank you.
谢谢
I mean,how's this gonna work, you know,with us?
我说，我们该如何处理此事?,你知道的…
When important decisions have to be made?
比方说某些重大的决定
- Give me a "for instance." - Well,I don't know.
- 举个例子  - 我也说不上来
- How about with the baby's name? - Marlon.
- 比方说孩子的名字  - 马龙
If it's a boy. Minnie,if it's a girl.
如果是个男孩马龙,如果是个女孩就叫米妮
As in "Mouse"?
和米老鼠的女友同名?
As in my grandmother.
和我奶奶同名
Still,you say "Minnie," you hear "Mouse."
不管怎样,听到这个还是想到老鼠
How about..?
这个怎么样…？
How about Julia?
朱莉亚？
- Julia. - We agreed on Minnie.
- 朱莉亚  - 我们决定用米妮
We agreed we'd spend our lives together.
真幽默，我们曾决定共同生活一辈子
Things change. Roll with the punches.
世事难料，兵来将挡
I believe Julia's on the table?
朱莉亚，就这么决定
Sorry about that.
抱歉
So,what have you been up to?
近来可好?
Oh,not much.
混得过去
- I got a job. - That's great.
- 我刚找到工作  - 这太好了
Why are you so tan?
你为何晒得这么黑?
I went to Aruba.
我到阿鲁巴了
Oh,no. You went on our honeymoon alone?
你自己一个去渡蜜月?
No.
不是的
I went with..
我和…
- Now,this may hurt. - Me?
- 你也许会很不好受  - 我?
No.
不
I went with Mindy.
我和明蒂去了
Mindy?
明蒂?
My maid of honor,Mindy?
我的伴娘明蒂?
Yeah,we're kind of a thing now.
对，我们是认真的
You got plugs!
你去做植发了?
Careful. They haven't quite taken yet.
小心，还不固定
And you got lenses.
你还配了隐形眼镜?
You hate sticking your finger in your eye.
你不是讨厌将手指放进眼镜吗?
Not for her.
还不是为了她
Listen,I really wanted to thank you.
我真的得感谢你
Okay.
好
A month ago,I wanted to hurt you more than I've ever wanted to.
一个月前我想伤害你,我从未如此激动过
And I'm an orthodontist.
我是个整牙医师
You know,you were right. I thought we were happy.
你说得没错,我以为我们会过得很快乐
We weren't happy.
我们不快乐
But with Mindy..
但是和明蒂在一起
now I'm happy.
现在我很快乐
- Spit. - What?
-吐掉  -什么?
Me.
是和我说
Anyway..
总之
I guess this belongs to you. Or maybe some day Mindy.
这东西属於你的,或许以后是明蒂的
Like she'd settle for that.
好像她现在已经开始为这个做准备了
Yeah,that's true.
是的，看来是真的
But I think it's a nice ring..
我觉得这是一个不错的戒指
and thank you for giving it to me.
谢谢你送我
Thank you for giving it back.
谢谢你送还给我
Hello!
你好!
- Please,what's wrong with Helen? - Helen Geller?
- 拜托，海伦有什么不好?  - 海伦盖勒?
- I don't think so. - It's not gonna be Helen Geller.
- 不行  - 她不会叫海伦盖勒的
- Thank you. - No,I mean,it's not Geller.
- 谢谢 - 不，我是说她不姓盖勒
It'll be Helen Willick?
难道她叫海伦威利克
No,actually,we talked about Helen Willick Bunch.
老实说,我们考虑用海伦威利克班奇
Wait a minute. Why is she in the title?
等等，为何有她的份?
It's my baby too.
因为她也是我的宝宝
Really? I don't remember you making any sperm.
真的?我不记得女人也会制造精子
And we all know what a challenge that is.
我们都知道那是个极大的挑战
- You two,stop it. - She gets a credit. I'm in there too.
- 够了，你们两个，别吵了  - 不，功劳全让她抢了,我也在场
Helen Willick Bunch Geller? I think that borders on child abuse.
你该不会想用海伦威利克班奇盖勒吧?  因为这有虐待儿童之嫌
Of course not. I'm suggesting Geller Willick Bunch.
当然没有,我想用盖勒威利克班奇
See what he does? He knows no one's gonna say all those names.
绝对不行,你看他,没人会叫她全名的
They'll call her Geller. He gets his way.
他知道别人只会叫她盖勒  这样他就得逞了
My way? You think this is my way?
我得逞?你认为这样算我得逞?
Of all the ways I ever imagined this moment being..
相信我，我没想到自己会沦落到这种地步
this is not my You know what? This is too hard.
我是不得已的…这很辛苦的
Knock,knock. How are we? Any nausea?
有人在吗? 今天如何，想呕吐吗?
- A little. - Just a little.
- 一点点  - 只是一点点
I was wondering about the mother-to-be,but thanks for sharing.
我只是问准妈妈,很感谢你们的分享
- Lie back. - You know what? I'm gonna go.
- 躺好  - 知道吗?我不加入
I don't think I can be involved in this family thing.
我认为此时自己无法淌入这浑水
- Oh,my God! - Look at that.
- 我的天呀  - 快看啊
I know.
我知道
Well,isn't that amazing?
很神奇吧
What are we supposed to be seeing here?
我们该看什么?
I don't know,but I think it's about to attack the Enterprise.
我不知道，可能是攻击企业号(星舰迷航记)
If you tilt your head and relax your eyes..
如果你们把头稍微向左偏，两眼放轻松
it kind of looks like an old potato.
它样子就像是一个颗老马铃薯
Then don't do that,all right?
那么就不要那么干
Monica,what do you think?
摩妮卡，你认为呢?
- Are you welling up? - No.
- 你热泪盈眶  - 才没有
- You are. You're welling up. - I'm not.
- 我只是…  - 你有，你热泪盈眶
- You're gonna be an aunt. - Oh,shut up.
- 你就要成为阿姨了  - 闭嘴
Hi,Mindy. Hi,it's Rachel.
明蒂，我是瑞秋
Yeah,I'm fine. I saw Barry today.
我很好，我今天和巴瑞见面了
Yeah,he told me. No,it's okay. Really,it's okay.
对，他告诉我了 不，没关系，真的
I hope you two are very happy. I really do.
我祝福你们幸福快乐,真心诚意的
And,Min,you know, if everything works out..
如果一切顺利
and you guys get married and have kids..
你们结婚生子
I hope they have his hairline and your nose!
希望他们有他的发线和你的鼻子
That was a cheap shot, but I feel so much better now!
我知道这招很贱，但我感觉好棒